alacrastore.com 2007-12-11

# AlacraStore.com - Privacy Policy

**The Alacra Store Privacy Policy**

Alacra, Inc. (" ** _Alacra_** ") is committed to protecting the privacy of Alacra Store Users who visit us at [www.alacrastore.com](http://www.alacrastore.com/). The following outlines our privacy and data protection policy. 

**Collection and use of User details**  
Personal details of Users of the **Alacra Store** will be collected and processed upon registration at our website. 

All personally identifiable information ("PII") of Users (including name, e-mail address, zip code, occupation, expected uses of information obtained from the Alacra Store is collected with the knowledge of Alacra Store Users via the website's order and registration forms only. Children under 13 years of age are not permitted to use the Alacra Store). 

PII is collected by Alacra for the following purposes: 

  * for order fulfillment
  * to notify Users of relevant new products and
  * to notify Users of promotional activities having to do with the Alacra Store and across Alacra's business generally; and
  * to analyze which Alacra products will be most appropriate for a particular customer

PII is retained by Alacra for in-house research to: 

  * improve our understanding of customer needs and product development;
  * build marketing profiles;
  * aid strategic development; and
  * manage our relationship with advertisers.

All results of such research and analysis will be anonymized or aggregated information and will not reveal any PII or other personal facts about individual Users. 

Alacra will not rent, sell, or otherwise disclose your PII with other people or companies except under the following circumstances: 

  * We may disclose your PII to other companies (e.g., data processors or fulfillment companies) that work on behalf of Alacra (including, if you provide us with your credit card information, credit card companies). These companies may also use your PII to help Alacra communicate with you about offers in which you may have expressed an interest. However, these companies do not have any right to use any of your PII that they receive from Alacra on their own behalf and they will be under an obligation to keep your personal information confidential. 
  * We may disclose your PII in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  * We may disclose your PII in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Alacra's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We may disclose or transfer your PII if Alacra is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Alacra will notify you before your PII is so disclosed or transferred if it becomes subject to a significantly different privacy policy.

Alacra currently operates from offices in the United States and the United Kingdom, but may operate from additional offices worldwide in the future. Steps have been taken to ensure that consistently high standards of data protection are adhered to in all Alacra offices for all the forms of processing mentioned above. 

**User choices**  
All registration and order forms provide Users with a series of choices regarding further promotional activity, forms of communication, and third party processing. 

When filling out order or registration forms on www.alacrastore.com, Users may be asked to indicate whether they are receptive to the use of e-mail to inform them of further Alacra promotional literature. If you would like to be kept informed of further Alacra products, as well as technical and functional developments related to our website and online services, please check the corresponding e-mail opt-in box. 

You may also be asked to indicate whether you wish to receive such information from companies with which Alacra does business. If you choose to receive such information, please be aware that Alacra is not responsible for the activities of such companies. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small file that is placed on the User's hard drive during a visit to a website. A cookie subsequently allows the User to move quickly and easily around the site by keeping a record of their activities during that visit and/or previous visits. Cookies in use at the Alacra Store are not associated with any PII about the User. 

Cookies can be deleted from a PC's hard drive at any time by the User, but such deletion may result in User needing to re-login to use the Alacra Store. 

**Security policy**  
Alacra will maintain appropriate measures to ensure that Users' personal details are not misused, accidentally destroyed, lost or altered within Alacra's server environment. All PII is encrypted for transmission over the Internet to Alacra's servers. 

**Transfer of PII overseas**  
Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing the Alacra Store and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of your PII in this way. 

**Updating customer details**  
It is important to Alacra that we have your correct contact information so that you do not miss out on further correspondence or experience problems with the delivery of products or services. To notify us of any changes, simply send your new details, along with your old details to Alacra using this this form(login required) to submit your changes. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**  
Beginning January 1, 2005 under California's "Shine the Light" law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2005 will receive information regarding 2004 sharing activities). 

To obtain this information on behalf of Alacra Inc, please send an email message to [CA.Privacy@alacrastore.com](mailto:CA.Privacy@alacrastore.com) with "Request for California Privacy Information" on the subject line and in the body of your message. We will provide the requested information to you at your e-mail address in response. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Alacra may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. However, if policy changes are implemented, which would materially and adversely affect the online privacy of our visitors, we will notify you by sending a notice to the e-mail address that you have most recently provided us with or by placing a prominent notice on our website. If you have any questions about our online privacy policies or information we may have stored about you, please contact our Chief Privacy Officer: 

Alacra,Inc.  
100 Broadway, Suite 1101   
New York, New York 10005   
United States   
Attn: Chief Privacy Officer

Effective date of this Privacy Policy: August 1st, 2005
